tuoitrenews.vn 2012-06-13

# Privacy-policy - TuoiTreNews

PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting Tuoitrenews Online, an online English language publication of Tuoi Tre newspaper. 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, this statement explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site.

**How We Collect and Use Your Personal Information**

We collect information through our optional user registration form and by users' voluntary participation in our polls and surveys. Individual profiles are neither compiled nor shared. 

**Registering**

Users have the option to register their contact information and personal information such as username, email address, place of residence, use of our website and age. This information will be used to create statistical data. Your individual profile is neither compiled nor shared. 

**Links**

Our site contains links to other websites. Once you leave the Tuoitrenews Online site, we are no longer responsible for the practices, policies or privacy issues of other sites.

Please be aware that every site has its own privacy policies. We encourage you to read these policies.

**Surveys and Polls**

Participation in our surveys and polls is completely voluntary. Contact information will be used to notify our results. This information will not be shared outside Tuoitrenews Online.

**Security**

Our websites take every precaution to protect our users' information. Your information will be protected both online and offline. 

**Correcting or Updating Personal Information**

Please email us if you need any of your personal information updated or changed.

e: ttn@tuoitre.com.vn
